http://www.flagbeach.com/cookie-policy/

Cookie policy
Cookie policy
This cookie statement was last updated on 9th July 2020 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.1. IntroductionOur website, https://flagbeach.com (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on "Save preferences", you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this cookie statement. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.5.1 Manage your consent settings6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping basket until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimise the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.7. Placed cookiesBaseBook
We use BaseBook for online appointments.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
course-filters
2 years
Stores course filters set in the BaseBook application
flagbeach_registrant_data
2 years
Stores registrant data stored in the BaseBook application
transient_accommodation_id
30 mins
Stores accommodation ID for use with the BaseBook application
flagbeach_booking_notes
30 mins
Stores booking notes used in the BaseBook registration process
flagbeach_booking_pax
30 mins
Stores number of visitors recorded in the BaseBook registration process
transient_package_id
30 mins
Stores Package ID used in the BaseBook application
cartItems
2 years
Stores items in the BaseBook cart
flagbeach_flight_details
30 mins
Stores flight details uploaded in the BaseBook registration process
flagbeach_booking_dates
30 mins
Stores Booking Dates requested in the BaseBook registration process
transient_course_id
Stores course ID during booking process
package-filters
2 years
Stores Package Filters used in the BaseBook application
FinalisedBooking
Stores booking details
Preferences
accommodation-filters
Stores accomodation filters selected by user
booknow-filters
Stores filters during booking process
Sharing
For more information, please read the BaseBook Privacy Policy.Yandex Metrica
We use Yandex Metrica for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
_ym_uid
2 years
_ym_retryReqs
Function
Statistics (anonymous)
_ga
2 years
_gid
1 day
Count and track pageviews
Statistics
_gat_UA-*
session
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Policy.Matomo
We use Matomo for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics (anonymous)
_pk_ses*
30 minutes
_pk_id*
13 months
Store a unique user ID
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.Google Tag Manager
We use Google Tag Manager for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
uslk_inital_url
persistent
uslk_referrer
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Tag Manager Privacy Policy.Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Policy.Google Maps
We use Google Maps for maps display. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Maps API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Maps Privacy Policy.YouTube
We use YouTube for video display. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
GPS
session
Store location data
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Policy.Miscellaneous
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
_ym*_reqNum
_ym*_lastHit
_ym*_lsid
_fbp
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Flag Beach Windsurf & Kitesurf Centre, Fuerteventura
Apto de Correos 285
35660 Corralejo
Fuerteventura
Canary Islands
Spain
Spain
Website: https://flagbeach.com
Email: info@flagbeach.com
Phone number: 00 34 928 866389This cookie policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 9th July 2020
Close
Sports
Kite Surfing Surfing Wind Surfing Wing Foiling SUP Catamaran About
Team Your stay A history of Flag Beach Jobs Our location Contact us Courses
Kitesurfing Surfing Windsurfing SUP Catamaran Wing Foil Packages
Kitesurfing Surfing Windsurfing Accommodation Equipment Beach Bag
EN
ES
DE
